[
	{
		"questionNum": "1",
		"question": "What weapon does Thor carry?",
		"answer": "A hammer",
		"choice1": "A sword",
		"choice2": "A hammer",
		"choice3": "A bow and arrow",
		"choice4": "A crossbow"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "2",
		"question": "What is the name of Black Panther’s home Country?",
		"answer": "Wakanda",
		"choice1": "Chad",
		"choice2": "Uganda",
		"choice3": "Wakanda",
		"choice4": "Rwanda"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "3",
		"question": "How many Infinity Stones are there",
		"answer": "Six",
		"choice1": "Five",
		"choice2": "Six",
		"choice3": "Four",
		"choice4": "Three"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "4",
		"question": "Which of the following characters can’t pick up Thor’s hammer?",
		"answer": "Loki",
		"choice1": "Thor",
		"choice2": "Captain America",
		"choice3": "Vision",
		"choice4": "Loki"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "5",
		"question": "What is Clint Barton’s superhero name?",
		"answer": "Hawkeye",
		"choice1": "Hawkman",
		"choice2": "Green Arrow",
		"choice3": "Falcon",
		"choice4": "Hawkeye"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "6",
		"question": "Which beloved comic book writer has cameoed in every Marvel movie up to Avengers: Endgame?",
		"answer": "Stan Lee",
		"choice1": "Frank Millar",
		"choice2": "Alan Moore ",
		"choice3": "Stan Lee",
		"choice4": "John Byrne"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "7",
		"question": "Who Killed Tony Stark’s parents?",
		"answer": "The Winter Soldier",
		"choice1": "The Winter Soldier",
		"choice2": "Mandarin",
		"choice3": "Whiplash ",
		"choice4": "Obadiah Stane"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "8",
		"question": "What is the name of the organization revealed to have taken over S.H.I.E.L.D in Captain America: The Winter Soldier?",
		"answer": "Hydra",
		"choice1": "The Hand",
		"choice2": "A.I.M",
		"choice3": "Hydra",
		"choice4": "Masters of Evil"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "9",
		"question": "What is the name of Thor’s father?",
		"answer": "Odin",
		"choice1": "Odin",
		"choice2": "Loki ",
		"choice3": "Tyr",
		"choice4": "Zeus"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "10",
		"question": "Complete the quote from Tony Stark’s daughter: I love you-",
		"answer": "3000",
		"choice1": "Tons",
		"choice2": "3000",
		"choice3": "So much",
		"choice4": "300"
	}
]
